One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Pirates vs. CP9
This is probably the place.
I finally made it.
I had to go
up and down all those stairs.
Robin!
Hey! Robin!
It's me!
Robin!
Where are you?!
Dammit!
That damn pigeon guy!
Oh, yeah...!
I know where they're going.
I should just head to the
Gates of Justice, too!
You have the key
to Robin's handcuffs, right?
Want to give it to me
before I take you down?
That's a foolish question.
I was disappointed that I didn't
get to see your real ability...
at the Galley-La mansion.
I never thought that pirates
would come this far, either, so...
Be careful;
I've grown far stronger since then.
I can imagine,
with all that energy you've got...
Energy like that of a beast.
What a fearsome man you are.
However,
my swordsmanship is the best in CP9.
Don't underestimate me.
Two-Sword Style, huh?
Tempest Kick.
So, no... sorry, but I use four swords.
No problem.
Come to think of it,
your entire body is a weapon.
72...
Tempest Kick.
– Pound Phoenix!
– White Thunder!
Shave!
This is fun!
I don't have time to have fun!
Then you just have to take me down.
Tempest Kick!
Tumult!
He controls these slashing attacks so easily.
You bastard... Are you mocking me?
Whoa... I'd expect no less from you.
If you're in that much
of a hurry, I'll show you...
my new powers.
Wh... What the hell?!
At any rate, what the heck is this room?
Someone really went nuts on the gardening.
This is practically outside!
No, no...
More importantly, I have to get
the key to Robin's handcuffs right now!
That key...!
Quietly...
Don't hesitate!
If I quietly grab it,
then quietly run away...
I'll accomplish my mission.
It'll be a flawless victory!
That's right.
I'm the king of being lucky!
I'm almost there!
A-A rooster?!
Oh, no! What is the noisiest
bird of them all doing here?
Oh, no!
If it crows, it's all over!
If it crows, he'll get up,
find me, and kill me!
Hey.
What're you looking at?!
Are you trying to crow?
Are you?! Are you?!
Shhh! Shhh!
Rooster-kun! Rooster-san!
Rooster-sama! I beg you!
Please don't crow!
Don't crow!
Don't! Please don't!
No rooster would crow like that!
Oh, you're here, pirate.
Th-That damn rooster!
Well, I guess it's time
I give you a beatdown.
That damn rooster!
H-He's strong...
So you're the one who came?!
You're the one who shot through
the government flag, right?
Jug reads "Liquor".
It seems that you're a skilled sniper.
He delivered a punch like that
right after he woke up?
Sorry for attacking you half-assed.
Forgive me.
It must've hurt.
Huh?
Don't worry.
I may not look like it,
but I'm not into tormenting my opponent.
A-A devil fruit...!
The Dog Dog Fruit, Model: Wolf!
I'll just tear out your windpipe
and that'll be it.
You'll die anyway.
You don't have to suffer.
Isn't that right?
W-Wolf...!
D-Dammit!
What?! Are you gonna fight?
You don't look strong, though.
S-Strong or not, I'm gonna fight!
Shut up!
I came to rescue Robin!
Whoa! The ceiling is...
collapsing!
Oh, shoot!
I was gonna
stop the transformation...
when I reached my hybrid form,
but I became a giraffe!
A talking giraffe is falling toward us!
Kaku!
That power of yours is too cool!
A wolf?!
What is this place?! A zoo?!
The Ox Ox Fruit, Model: Giraffe!
You poor guy!
To think that you'll be
a giraffe man for the rest of your life!
What's wrong with giraffes?!
I said I like it!
That pigeon guy
was a leopard, wasn't he?
There are two more ability users who transform into animals...
Is CP9 that kind of group?
S-So they are zoan-type ability users?
A wolf man and a giraffe man...
I got stuck with a scary one!
But Zoro falling with that giraffe saved me.
While it appears to be a two-versus-two fight,
I'll just wait for Zoro to do most of the work.
What's that?
It looks like a safe
with the door left opened.
Whoa!
Could those
weird-looking handcuffs be...?!
I said don't laugh!
Hey, giraffe!
Just how long are you gonna
stand there arguing with him?
I thought I told you
that I don't have much time.
If you wanna keep arguing,
I'll just cut you down where you stand.
How foolish... Don't underestimate a
giraffe's limitless destructive power.
Transform...
Hybrid Form!
I'll show you...
the power of my transformation!
How lame!
Gasp!
What'd you just...?
Why'd I blurt something like that out?!
I shouldn't have said that.
I was so shocked
that I just blurted it out!
Don't lose your composure, Zoro!
It will dull your blades!
Just how long are you gonna
keep laughing, Jabra?!
S-Sorry.
In any case, he looks funny.
How the hell does this form
reflect his square features?
Wh-What're these handcuffs?!
Ahhh!
Shoot! I'm sorry, Zoro-kun!
Hey! What're you doing?!
Th-They're probably seastone handcuffs just like Robin's!
Since our enemies are both
devil fruit ability users.
I thought they'd be weaker if
they were handcuffed with them!
So why are they on me, you idiot?!
B-Because...
the giraffe's face is so
funny that I just lost my grip.
A giraffe with square everything...
He's right!
Damn all of you!
Taste the power of an ability user!
Tempest Kick!
Whoa! What's that?!
He's gonna do something!
Sky Slicer!
This isn't good.
Duck, Usopp!
I see...
Your strength is in your length—
in other words, your reach.
With the power coming from that huge
body and the centrifugal force,
your attacks are deeper
and sharper than before.
Wh-What the heck?!
Hey, I don't see any damage.
Look at the ceiling.
Huh? The ceiling?
Oh?
I can see the blue sky.
Whoa...
I wonder why... Hm...?
Don't tell me the
Tower of Justice has been cut in two!
Hey, hey, hey, hey...!
This is dangerous!
How shameful!
You betrayed your emotions during a battle!
Shut up.
I like being a giraffe.
I love giraffes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No matter how sharp your attacks are,
they won't intimidate me at all.
S-Stop it, Zoro!
That hurts! What're you doing?!
Why are you pulling my arm?!
Huh...? Pulling my arm?
Whoa! It's locked tight!
Hey! What're you doing?!
It's not my fault, is it?!
This happened because you charged at me!
I did that because you were standing
there in a daze when he attacked!
Just unlock these handcuffs!
What're these guys doing?
Beats me.
To put it simply,
this means that we're
in the same situation as Robin is.
Then, the key is...
in the hands of one
of the CP9 members.
We have no choice but to beat them and get their keys.
Don't be absurd!
There's no way we can fight like this!
Our prey are locked together.
Okay then, Jabra.
Just stand back
and leave these two to me.
What?! Are you trying to snatch my prey?!
So, do you want to work
together and fight them?
I'd rather die.
Me, too.
Hey, you two!
Tell us the number on those handcuffs.
Number?
The handcuffs and the keys have numbers
so that we know which key
unlocks which handcuffs.
If those handcuffs can be unlocked
by one of the keys we have,
we'll unlock them right away.
What?! Really?!
The number... where's the number?
Here it is! It's 2!
Unlock them!
Not the right one.
Mine isn't, either.
Sorry.
What?! You got my hopes up, you jerks!
Damn it!
Then, it means one of the other three
CP9 members has the right one, huh?
I guess we have no choice.
The first one to get a kill wins.
Seems like that's the only way.
What?!
Tower of Justice
Inner Chamber
Whoa! What's with these stairs?!
They're sliced in two and out of place.
The impact from earlier...
As I suspected,
something must've happened.
Is this building okay?
Hey! Are you okay?!
Ah! Zoro! Sogeking!
Ah! Hey! Chopper!
What's going on? They're waving to me.
It looks kinda fun.
H-Hey, guys!
Idiot!
Look at the handcuffs!
Find the key for the no. 2 handcuffs!
Huh? A key?
What the hell is this?!
I just assumed that there'd
be a bridge or something.
What crazy huge whirlpools!
I can see the Gates of Justice now,
but is it possible to get
there on a regular boat?
Whatever. I don't have much time.
I guess I'll try something.
Here we go!
Just wait, Robin!
I see.
So the handcuffs and the keys
have numbers on them.
What?!
That's what's happening here?
Then I'll fight these guys!
Don't be ridiculous!
There are two of them!
If you get taken out,
with these handcuffs on, we're dead for sure!
Please! You're our only hope!
Hope?
It's not like I'm
happy to hear that, you jerk!
Sanji, Nami, and Franky...
If any of them get the no. 2 key, bring it straight to us!
We're counting on you!
The one who's likely to get
the key first is... maybe Sanji?
I'll go look for Sanji.
I'm their only hope!
Now...
Level 0
Isolated Corridor
Nami vs. Kumadori
I've got you!
Let me go!
Yoyoi!
Just...
give up!
Die!
I'm no match for him at all!
Franky...
Iron Body!
Boxing!
Shave!
Hallway in Front of the Pantry
Franky vs. Fukuro
What's with your punches?
You're no ordinary human!
Even if you harden your body to make it like iron,
my fists are real iron.
N-No!
This is no time for having tea!
Kalifa's Room
Sanji vs. Kalifa
Witchcraft!
I was drawn in by your witchcraft!
I almost fell victim to a love trap as dangerous as a storm surge!
You've already had three cups.
Shut up, witch!
I'm not gonna
be caught in a trap again!
CP9 insulted Robin-chan
terribly on the sea train.
I'm not gonna forget about it.
Now...
give me the key!
That's too bad...
It seems like you're in a hurry.
Go ahead and take the key.
Where is it?
Well...
Where on my body do you think I hid it?
Why don't you try finding it?
I'd be happy to!
It's looking hopeless for you.
I'm an idiot.